Have you ever made a really big mistake?
Norbit is a comedy film directed by Brian Robbins.
A mild-mannered guy who is engaged to a monstrous woman meets the woman
of his dreams, and schemes to find a way to be with her.
Norbit / Rasputia / Mr. Wong, played by Eddie Murphy.
Kate Thomas, played by Thandiwe Newton.
Big Jack Latimore, played by Terry Crews.
Earl Latimore, played by Clifton Powell.
Blue Latimore, played by Lester Speight.
Deion Hughes, played by Cuba Gooding Jr..
Norbit is a 2007 American comedy film, directed by Brian Robbins, and
co-written by, co-produced by, and starring Eddie Murphy.
The film co-stars Thandie Newton, Terry Crews, Cuba Gooding Jr., Eddie
Griffin, Katt Williams, Marlon Wayans, and Charlie Murphy.
Murphy portrays multiple roles including the eponymous
Norbit and his abusive, obese wife Rasputia.
Norbit, unhappily married, is reunited with his childhood sweetheart Kate, but must contend
with Rasputia and her brothers and foil a sabotage plan constructed by Rasputia.
It was released by DreamWorks and Paramount Pictures on February 9, 2007.
The film was a box office success, grossing $159 million
worldwide against a production budget of $60 million.
It received generally negative reviews from critics and was
nominated for eight Golden Raspberry Awards.
The tone is lighthearted.